{
    "id": "e22d1bbdba324ca1b89db3bc5ce72f60",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I look forward ………………… seeing you soon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d16d9f05942049a2addee1dfbbc2e777"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate being shouted …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b4d9ad0d1cfb43f9b4fd75c42d1645df"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are all anxious …………………… an end to this misunderstanding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b940f9d8e45e4ce69b85e85a9cdbfaf6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She accused me ................................. poisoning her cat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1b2a2e887e424907b2d5e292be9c18ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "She saved money ................................ giving up coffee.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "70d9482862734a46a85bf3de5b890efd"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you believe ............................... yourself, you can do anything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f7839ab2fb714345bb4cf55a8805afff"
        },
        {
            "question": "I think the film is a bit weak ............................ the end.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "79391e00ee3742edaf5f00fdbe9ee226"
        },
        {
            "question": "He tripped ................................. the cat and fell downstairs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bb9a9c8760464716a97e59bf5a8e741d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate the thought ................................ going back to school.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d28a88f33af34813bec9f6915701057c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She rang me ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8b9d5207506f4ac29eb15baffc3c6d8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you belong ................................... any sports clubs?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "to",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3cee436d16c647f680bad53a03b2d6f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents never showed if they were disappointed .............................. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2a4c3e17ff6b48dfa1bceb5655d377c6"
        }
    ]
}